{
    "0": {
        "question": "how would you update channel branding to support a tour announcement?",
        "answer": ["upload a channel banner that includes the tour dates."]
    },
    "1": {
        "question": "how do playlists affect watch time on a channel?",
        "answer": ["playlists can increase watch time because viewers will often keep watching videos in a sequence."]
    },
    "2": {
        "question": "what\u2019s something that video cards can promote?",
        "answer": ["links to merch sites."]
    },
    "3": {
        "question": "what does not describe a thumbnail that has been optimized for discovery?",
        "answer": ["the thumbnail is&nbsp;low-resolution."]
    },
    "4": {
        "question": "what does a channel\u2019s search data reveal?",
        "answer": ["the keywords viewers are using to find the channel\u2019s videos."]
    },
    "5": {
        "question": "how can subscribers boost engagement, and thus discovery, for a video?",
        "answer": ["subscribers who have turned on notifications will generate the video\u2019s first wave of traffic."]
    },
    "6": {
        "question": "what type of video is designed to get fans excited about a new album or tour?",
        "answer": ["teasers or samplers."]
    },
    "7": {
        "question": "why is behind-the-scenes footage from a tour valuable for a channel?",
        "answer": ["all of the above."]
    },
    "8": {
        "question": "what is the most effective way to promote a collaboration on youtube?",
        "answer": ["produce a collaboration teaser and upload it to both collaborators\u2019 channels."]
    },
    "9": {
        "question": "which of the following accurately describes art tracks?",
        "answer": ["all of the above."]
    },
    "10": {
        "question": "how does upgrading to an official artist channel affect an artist\u2019s subscribers?",
        "answer": ["upgrading makes it easier for subscribers to find all of an artist\u2019s music in one place."]
    },
    "11": {
        "question": "how does an artist benefit from upgrading to an official artist channel?",
        "answer": ["the official artist channel appears at the top of search results for the artist."]
    },
    "12": {
        "question": "what is the best way to leverage fan videos to grow a channel?",
        "answer": ["drop fan videos into a playlist with a descriptive name."]
    },
    "13": {
        "question": "what is the best way to engage fans before an album release on youtube?",
        "answer": ["live stream a listening event."]
    },
    "14": {
        "question": "why is it important to keep uploading videos after an album release?",
        "answer": ["because it maintains or increases viewer engagement with the channel, which can increase album sales."]
    },
    "15": {
        "question": "what is the most effective way to encourage subscribers to engage with a channel?",
        "answer": ["upload videos on a regular schedule."]
    },
    "16": {
        "question": "why might you want to pin a fan comment on a video?",
        "answer": ["the comment says something positive about the video."]
    },
    "17": {
        "question": "how can you use community to give fans an inside look at a tour?",
        "answer": ["post a photo of the setlist."]
    },
    "18": {
        "question": "with which youtube feature can you establish a watch page before a video is released, so that an artist and their fans can experience a new video together?",
        "answer": ["premieres."]
    },
    "19": {
        "question": "what is one effective way to use the community tab?",
        "answer": ["post a mix of personal, promotional, and transactional posts to engage fans."]
    },
    "20": {
        "question": "what can tell you about the global reach of a channel?",
        "answer": ["geography data."]
    },
    "21": {
        "question": "what can you do to prevent a sudden drop in a video\u2019s audience retention chart?",
        "answer": ["ensure that the video\u2019s metadata accurately reflects the content."]
    },
    "22": {
        "question": "what should you do when a channel\u2019s demographics data describes an audience that\u2019s much different from the targeted audience?",
        "answer": ["revise the content strategy to focus on engaging the targeted audience."]
    },
    "23": {
        "question": "youtube analytics for artists provides data about what type of content?",
        "answer": ["an artist\u2019s songs across youtube."]
    },
    "24": {
        "question": "what can you learn from the data in music charts & insights?",
        "answer": ["the most popular music videos of the week in a given city or country."]
    },
    "25": {
        "question": "what\u2019s one practical application for youtube analytics for artists?",
        "answer": ["understand which of an artist\u2019s songs are fan favorites, and include these songs on a tour setlist."]
    },
    "26": {
        "question": "if you wanted to learn in which major city a competing artist\u2019s video is getting the most views this week, what might help you?",
        "answer": ["music charts and insights."]
    },
    "27": {
        "question": "what requirement must a video meet before it\u2019s eligible to earn ad revenue?",
        "answer": ["the content must be&nbsp;advertiser-friendly."]
    },
    "28": {
        "question": "which two parties most commonly enter into an srav (sound recording audio visual) agreement with each other?",
        "answer": ["youtube and record labels."]
    },
    "29": {
        "question": "who can monetize videos on youtube?",
        "answer": ["channels that have joined the youtube partner program, or channels that are linked to a label or distributor with an srav agreement."]
    },
    "30": {
        "question": "what is the goal of the ad-serving model?",
        "answer": ["to serve the&nbsp;highest-value&nbsp;ad to the right viewer at the right time."]
    },
    "31": {
        "question": "what deters advertisers from showing ads on a video?",
        "answer": ["explicit language."]
    },
    "32": {
        "question": "why might you want to review the ratio of views to ads shown on a video in two time periods?",
        "answer": ["to see how this ratio is trending over time."]
    },
    "33": {
        "question": "how can you estimate which ad formats are earning the most revenue?",
        "answer": ["use the ad rates report to compare the estimated revenue amounts generated from each ad type."]
    },
    "34": {
        "question": "what low-investment strategy could a channel try to increase viewership (and ad revenue) in another country?",
        "answer": ["leverage the audience to crowdsource captions and metadata translations."]
    },
    "35": {
        "question": "why might two videos with similar monetizable view counts earn different revenue?",
        "answer": ["different ad formats are enabled on the videos."]
    },
    "36": {
        "question": "what can generate additional revenue for an artist on youtube?",
        "answer": ["concert listings."]
    },
    "37": {
        "question": "can an artist promote a paid product or service on youtube?",
        "answer": ["yes, but the artist should be mindful of disclosure requirements and any&nbsp;third-party&nbsp;agreements."]
    },
    "38": {
        "question": "what can you do to maximize an artist\u2019s revenue potential in the youtube music app?",
        "answer": ["deliver the artist\u2019s entire catalog to youtube."]
    },
    "39": {
        "question": "why should an artist seek legal advice before uploading a cover song?",
        "answer": ["to determine whether the original song is protected by copyright."]
    },
    "40": {
        "question": "which types of copyright apply most often to music on youtube?",
        "answer": ["sound recording and musical composition."]
    },
    "41": {
        "question": "what happens to a channel when it receives a copyright takedown notice?",
        "answer": ["the offending video is removed and the channel owner receives a copyright strike."]
    },
    "42": {
        "question": "what is subject to a \u201cmatch\u201d in content id?",
        "answer": ["a video that contains content in the content id database."]
    },
    "43": {
        "question": "what is the difference between copyright and content id?",
        "answer": ["copyright is a set of laws, while content id is a tool that helps rights holders exercise their rights on youtube."]
    },
    "44": {
        "question": "how does content id support the work of music rights holders?",
        "answer": ["it enables them to monetize or otherwise protect their content on youtube."]
    },
    "45": {
        "question": "why is it important to resolve asset ownership conflicts quickly?",
        "answer": ["because conflicts can suspend any revenue generated from the videos in conflict."]
    },
    "46": {
        "question": "which asset type is always linked to a sound recording asset on youtube?",
        "answer": ["composition share."]
    },
    "47": {
        "question": "what may indicate that a channel needs to clean up its reference files or revise its match policies?",
        "answer": ["the channel sees an increase in claim disputes."]
    },
    "48": {
        "question": "what predefined match policy allows viewers to watch a claimed video but does not allow ads to display on the video?",
        "answer": ["track."]
    },
    "49": {
        "question": "where can you see the relationship between references and assets?",
        "answer": ["asset report."]
    }
}
